<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Anugerah&#39;s Digital Garden</title>
    <link>https://zesty-baklava-d1dd11.netlify.app/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Anugerah&#39;s Digital Garden</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 18:27:58 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zesty-baklava-d1dd11.netlify.app/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://zesty-baklava-d1dd11.netlify.app/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 22:45:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zesty-baklava-d1dd11.netlify.app/home/contact/</guid>
      <description>It seems like you are interested in me or my works. Find more about me and my contact!
Name Social Media Artworks Instagram Video Youtube Email nugehoodg@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Garden</title>
      <link>https://zesty-baklava-d1dd11.netlify.app/home/digital_garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 21:55:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zesty-baklava-d1dd11.netlify.app/home/digital_garden/</guid>
      <description>Digital Garden A Digital Garden is where people like you would publish their research, and or notes on the internet for people to see. You plant the seed, which is the idea, and it will eventually grow and becomes knowledge/article. There&amp;rsquo;s many way in which people uses Digital Garden for, they usually used it for:
Keeping (Storage) Decoding Sharing Those are just the main and obvious purpose of why people use Digital Garden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://zesty-baklava-d1dd11.netlify.app/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zesty-baklava-d1dd11.netlify.app/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello there! How are you doing?
My name is Anugerah and I am a university student from Lambung Mangkurat university, Banjarmasin, studying in the English Language Education Study Program. Before going into the university studying English Language, I was in vocational high school studying Software Engineering, that explained a lot about how I&amp;rsquo;m used to coding or programming.
NICE TO MEET YOU!
Education Sekolah Dasar Negara Alalak Tengah 1 Sekolah Menengah Pertama 13 Sekolah Menengah Vokasi 4 Lambung Mangkurat University (2021) Experiences UMKM Lambung Mangkurat Debate Society Member of Media and Design Division Kalimantan Open Debate 2022 Event Coordinator of Publication and Documentation Division Experties Advance English Language Proficiency Writing Speaking Graphic Design Social Media Post Poster Logo Video Editing Infographic Music Video Promotion Technical Experties Adobe Photoshop LaTex HTML CSS Markdown Vegas Pro Adobe Premiere Adobe After Effect Office LibreOffice Thanks Y&amp;rsquo;all!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
